Thanks to this paper, it takes
us into the realm of automated Thrombolysis in Cerebral Infarction
(TICI) scoring using deep learning.
I forked the source code provided by the paper
on Git Hub and successfully ported it to Colab.
Simply click the button to execute.
Now, please open the 'Runtime' menu
and select 'Change runtime type.’
Make sure you are using
Python 3 and GPU acceleration.
Let's start 'Run all' the code.
Run anyway
First, it will download and install
the PyTorch EfficientNet model.
Next, it will install the
SimpleITK and Pydicom libraries.
Next, it will load pre-defined functions and
model parameters. This process may take some time.
For ease of data upload, the program will pause at the 'input' function, waiting for your interaction.
1, Click the ‘Files’ icon on the left.
2, Click the ‘Upload to
session storage’ icon above.
Please select a set of DICOM files
from your local folder for prediction.
Please be patient while the
files are being uploaded.
After confirming that the files are displayed in the list, press Enter in the 'input' box to continue.
According to AI prediction, this DSA series
scores "TICI 3", with a probability of about 77%.
I have displayed the images from
the DSA series for visual reference, allowing human experts to compare.
The histogram of the DSA
series is also intriguing.
The final line of code will delete
the uploaded files to protect privacy.
If you would like to predict another set of data, please click the 'Predict' hyperlink
to return to the Predict section.
This time, please click on 'Run after' in the menu to avoid starting from the
beginning, saving an amount of time.
Upload the data.
Be patient.
Press Enter.
Predict score.
Verify the images.
Protecting privacy.
Thanks for watching and happy coding